yaksgames.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy - YaksGames.com

This privacy policy explains how Yaksgames.com treats personal information that we collect and receive. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing or using Our Websites, You acknowledge that You have read and understand the Policy, accept this Policy and agree to be bound by them. If You do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Service.

What information do we collect and use?

**1\. Data we receive from you**

Yaksgames.com does not require any personally identifiable information. However, if you send us an e-mail directly, we will optionally process the information, such as name, and email addresses.

**2\. Data we receive automatically**

When you visit our Websites, our web servers automatically store your computer's IP address. When you request a page from Yaksgames.com, our servers will record your IP address and we will trace and collect your whole activities on our page, such as browser type and version, geographical location, the operating system you use, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths, etc. This data is used to analyze the use of the Websites and to improve the Websites and services.

We can also collect some data using cookies, you can check out the details in the section “Use of Cookies” of this Policy.

How do we use your information?

We gather information to enable us to optimize the content and services and provide you with a customized experience on the Site. We will not sell or share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us.

**1\. We may use your personal data for statistical purposes, so we can operate and improve the services and our websites;**

**2\. We may use your personal data for marketing purpose, such as new games added daily and updates on existing games.**

**3\. We may use information gathered by the use of cookies for targeted advertisements and promotions.**

**4\. We may use anonymize and aggregate information for website traffic flow analysis, usage analysis, market analysis, reports, and marketing.**

Use of Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the computer when you visit a site. We use cookies to offer you a better browsing experience on our Websites. We might use cookies to analyze site traffic, provide social media features, understand user behavior so we can personalize content, and serve you with interest-based or targeted advertising.

Cookies do lots of different jobs and have different types, and most web browsers can be set to disable or clear cookies when cookies are placed on your device. Please check out our [Cookie Policy](https://yaksgames.com/cookie-policy) for more information on the use of cookies and other tracking technologies on our Services.

Privacy Practices of Third Parties

This privacy statement only addresses the use and disclosure of information by Us through Your interaction with Our Websites and Services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or content of Third party websites. When you leave the Site to a third party website by clicking a game or ad, we encourage you to view their privacy policies first.

Children and Privacy

Our site is not targeted to children under the age of 13. Children under the age of 13 must not use the Site for any purpose. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail. We also believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and use certain tools to help create a kid-friendly online environment for their children.

This Policy may be amended or updated from time to time to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. If we update this policy, changes will be reflected on this page. We also suggest you to read this policy carefully and regularly check this page to view and changes we might make.

Contact us

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [promospure@gmail.com](mailto:promospure@gmail.com "YaksGames Support email")
